We hope you enjoy your stay!
And don't forget to bring some of your belongings with you!
We will be performing at the Peach Color Singing Contest again this year.
We are in Yokoyari right now,
I was kind of nervous in the big room with all the idols.
I was a little nervous in the big room with all the idols.
I'm nervous.
It's so cute.
The space is so cute, I'm overwhelmed.
There are so many people.
He's famous.
It's so cute.
I'm so happy.
Next time preview
This sky is the trigger.
Last, this sky is the trigger.
It's been a while.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time since I've done the trigger.
It's been so long.
When we rehearsed, I didn't know.
I don't know.
I didn't know what it was. I was like, "I don't know what it is.
I'm looking forward to today because Maika will be born after a long time.
That's right. As soon as I'm done, I'm going to go to Countdown TV.
I've been busy. You know, Maika always said she wanted to be very busy. I'm kind of busy. You know, Maika, you always said you wanted to be very busy.
Yes, that's what you said.
I'm extremely busy, aren't I?
Yes, I was thinking that earlier.
I'm happy.
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
Please do your best.
I will do my best.
Today is the last day of the year,
In five or six hours, this year will be over,
I don't really feel it,
I feel like I'm floating in the air,
I'm floating in the air, or rather, I'm feeling a little flustered,
I'm nervous and it's been a long time. I'm sorry. It's been a long time.
I was sleeping earlier, so I'm wearing a mask.
Everyone is so cute, I'm so nervous,
But I'm not going to let this atmosphere get the better of me,
I hope you will think that I'm amazing, as you often do in collaboration,
I hope you will think I'm a great collaborator,
I will do my best with a lot of smiles and freshness,
I will do my best. I will do my best.
Today, we will be performing on a stage like a center stage,
I will enjoy myself to the fullest. I will find a lot of things. I'm looking forward to seeing you all.
Hello, everyone. Today is December 31, 2023. It is New Year's Eve.
So, what a year,
I have been invited to appear on Momoi no Atagashi.I have been invited to appear at Momoi no Atagashi.
Thank you very much. Really.
It's an event I've been longing to attend for a long time,
This year, this event is the last one. I'm a little nervous, but I think I'm looking forward to it,
I am a little nervous, but I am looking forward to it.
We, NotEqual Me, are going to perform "Where are the angels?
We spent a lot of time on it this year.
It is a single, so I am very grateful to be able to perform it, and I am looking forward to doing my best. I will do my best!
Today is the Momoshiki Uta Gassen (Peach Color Song Contest).
I'm really excited about everything,
I'm really nervous about everything, but I'll do my best.
I'll be at the lever in just a little while,
I will do my best to bring you a happy New Year's Eve.
I hope that I can do a half twin today and finish the Milten Festival safely.
I will do my best!
Today is New Year's Eve 2023.
I'm going to the first Peach Color Singing Contest!
I am nervous. My hands are sweating.
I will do my best!
So, what is your last goal for this year?
Yes!
Good job!
You did your best, didn't you, Sekkan?
I did my best!I did my best!
I did my best!
I, at the end, want to do my best already.
Be sparkling,
Now, since you have given us this opportunity, let's have fun together.
Yes!
Se-no, tatekoshi-yes!
I'll do my best!
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching!
Q. What are your future goals?
It was a lot of fun.
But please don't be greedy.
How many times have you done this?
We've shot a lot.
It's amazing.
Look forward to the next one!
It's not just for the super stage, either.
Indeed.
You and the rest of you were warm and welcoming.
Thank you very much.
I knew Chiara got the last title wrong too.
The first trigger is in a totally different position. The first trigger position is totally different.
It's different.
Crime.
Wrong front.
In rehearsal maybe, yesterday.
I thought they weren't there at all, so I thought it was a different song.
I pushed something.
It's this way!
At first, when I started the song, the members would look at each other, and they would laugh.
Someone laughs.
Surprisingly, I don't know.
I have to be a little more gruff.
A little more.
Where is it?
He said it's definitely this way.
It's definitely this way.
Rehearsal.
It was the best Chiara until the end.
The best Chiara in 23 years.
Please do me a favor.
Please try to do it right too.
No, you can't. If you do it like this alone.
I'm sure.
How was it, doctor?
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
We are now on the collaboration stage.
Hitomi-chan will be on.
I'm nervous.
It's the next day, so I'll do my best.
You can't miss it.
I was watching everyone's UFOs while I was alone.
She's doing her best.
It's cute.
I put a ribbon on it.
It's a heart-shaped virus.
Maichirun, Arie and I will be doing it together.
I would like to get along with the microphone stand and the tambourine.
Thank you for watching!
What's coming up this summer?
The end of the year!
Year end!
End of the year!
I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little nervous, but I'm going to dance as much as I can
I'll do my best!
It's over!
I was so nervous!
It was fun!
It was really fun! It was really fun!
So many of my favorite idols came together.
It was a really great experience!
It was really a wonderful experience!
Thank you so much!
Minium's store
Oh! Did you eat everything?
We all ate...
Minium
Minium, there's a place like this.
June!
After all we've been through... all those peaks and valleys...
We've been through so much already.
They don't laugh at me.
It's like eating.
It's delicious.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's wrong?
I'm a mess.
I can eat it without teeth.
What?
Oh, no!
I can eat without teeth.
Oh no! Oh my God!!!
And the best.
I ate my dinner and then I ate the last of it.
It's my teacher's favorite candy.
Oh! I love this!
I love this!
Oh, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Cute!
Too cute.
Thank you!
I'm going to appear on Countdown TV Live Live now!
I'm off!
I'll be there!
I'll do my best!
Bye bye!
Good luck!
Thanks for all your hard work while we missed the last one.
Thank you very much.
It was my first time to be a Momoiro Uta Sensor,
I was very impressed with your performance, I was very happy to deliver the last performance,
I was very happy to be able to deliver the final performance at Matsumatsu.
I was so happy to be able to perform as a collaboration maid,
We were allowed to wear Momoiro costumes,
We danced the UFO,
At first sight, our hearts stood out.
Every stage was really fun to watch,
We also had a lot of fun performing on the stage,
I hope we will be able to come back again, bigger and more powerful.
I hope we will be able to come back again, bigger and better.
And from Momoilo-san, too,
When we started filming, I received a lot of letters and 200-yen gifts,
I was able to put all my energy into it,
I hope that our power has reached you all.
I hope our power has reached you all.
We are going to have a wonderful New Year's Eve.
Thank you very much.